As you well
know
,
I have been feeling very
tired and with
mixed
feelings due to the huge changes that have taken place in my life over the past few weeks
.  I've noticed that
my creativity leaves
me when I'm stressed
.    When
I feel like painting again, creating something new, decorating,
that's a great
sign that I'm recovering.
So, to get that
creativity
back
, I decided to decorate my
house with something
new
.  Due to work pressure
and
lack of time,
I neglected the box containing wedding gifts and some new and old items
.  Finally, I decided to not only
clean my house
, but also
add a bit of newness and beauty to it
.  Oscar
Wilde once
said, "You
must be exactly who you are,
because everyone else
already has who they are
."  When I
first
heard that,
it seemed very
clever
.
As I grew older and saw the world,
I
came to know the true meaning of that word.  It is very easy to set aside our true personality
, to become someone we are not
.    We
spend time living in our own shadow, unable to accept certain parts of ourselves
.  I did that for a long
time
;  I was afraid to admit to myself, worried that I would look strange, while explaining my
interests to
others
.  It's great to move forward beyond that fear
.  As for me
, as a
creative
person,
decorating my home with different colors and innovative details gives
me great
satisfaction
.  So,
today I want
to show you some small chores I've been doing at home
.  If you look around
you will
see that
I am inspired by books and movies that depict nature and imaginary things in a wonderful way
.  In particular,
I
love films that are hand-painted by artists.
Growing up,
I used to be a bit
shy about watching animated movies
, and wouldn't talk about it unless other people
liked it
.  To explain why we shouldn't be ashamed of what we
like
, I'll
use this habit of mine as an example.
Because if you know
why you like something and
you're comfortable with it
,
you can enjoy it without fear
.  For example,
I
like animated films
because they are the
collaborative work of many artists.
That is very
hard
work.  The movies I
love the most
aim to make the audience imagine other possibilities, question the limits of this world, romanticize life, and celebrate hope and friendship even in the midst of pain and hardship
.  They
seem fun, interesting to me,
and
feel safe
because I
associate them with warm, positive memories of childhood.
Some examples of
movies I love are
Maya's
amazing
animations,
Wind in the
Willows from 1995,
Song of the Sea
, Hilda, and The
Tales of
Beatrix
Potter.  There are so many
favorite
movies and shows
.  My love for this
strange and
magical thing is
reflected in my home.
So, while I was collecting flowers
from the garden to decorate the house
, these little
flowers
appeared.
These just bloomed the other day
so
I didn't know they were growing, and
I
don't even remember planting snapdragons.    Whenever
I saw these in the garden as a child
, I would talk to them and the gods of the magical
world
.  Yes,
the next time
you see these snapdragons in your garden
,
try talking to the gods with them
.  Maybe it
can work.
Who knows?
I hope some of you will receive it this week
.  Take a minute to take a journal
or
mentally write down not only what you
like
, but
why you
like it
and what
it tells you about it
.
This is a
powerful
exercise
and can be
a step towards developing a friendship with yourself
.
Thank you everyone for all the kind words you have given to my last few videos.    The
love you have shown is very
valuable.
It
really
inspired me to reconnect with what I love about making videos and beautifying my home
.  It also
helped me complete small tasks that I had always wanted to complete.
I got so caught up in the busyness of work and
life that I couldn't make
time to finish the many things I was doing and try new things
.  That's why I
first took some
time off to motivate myself
.
I actually took a
whole
weekend for
myself
, and it felt so
luxurious
.    It's
really
wonderful to have a few days without any important tasks that need to be completed quickly
.  That made a lot of
difference
.
I read
most of my
favorite
books during that time
, and they
always
inspire my creativity at home
.  I also re-watched
my
favorite
childhood
movies for inspiration
,
because the things I
love about building a beautiful home are
directly
inspired by the books, art, and movies that were so important to me growing up.  I'm reminded again of
that small,
peaceful
part of me that gets neglected when I'm busy
.  All things
considered, I firmly believe that for a
house to feel
strange and
wonderful, it must have
life in it
.  Bringing plants into your
home,
or putting
nature-
inspired
paintings on the walls
, or having a
pet
, all of these things
make my home feel so vibrant and full of love.
And I
really
like that.
Anyway, I send my
love to you
all
.  I'm going to close my
Etsy shop for
a while
.  I'm not sure how long
, but
it could take a long time
because I have
other small
projects to
start
.  So, if
you would like to support this
channel in that
way
,
I would be very
grateful.
I put a sticker I created on every
order
and also include
a few
extra
items with each one
.  I wanted to find a way to express my gratitude for your
support
.  It means a lot to me at this time
.  If you're
near me at the end of August,
I'm doing a
book signing event at the end of that month
.    I am
providing the details below for those who are interested.    I do
n't expect many people to come because I'm in a remote area,
but if
you
can come that far, I'd love to
meet you,
but
no pressure.
Okay, I'm sending my
love to all of you
.  Thank you again for your
encouraging
words
, and I will
see you soon.
Goodbye.
Mmm.